export const verbPracticeDataDeutsch = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Ich", answer: "bin" },
    { prompt: "Du", answer: "bist" },
    { prompt: "Er", answer: "ist" },
    { prompt: "Sie", answer: "ist" },
    { prompt: "Es", answer: "ist" },
    { prompt: "bin", answer: "ich" },
    { prompt: "bist", answer: "du" },
    { prompt: "ist", answer: "er/sie/es" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Ich", answer: "habe" },
    { prompt: "Du", answer: "hast" },
    { prompt: "Er", answer: "hat" },
    { prompt: "Sie", answer: "hat" },
    { prompt: "habe", answer: "ich" },
    { prompt: "hast", answer: "du" },
    { prompt: "hat", answer: "er/sie/es" }
  ]
};
